Guide to the Edward J Wormley and Edward Crouse Papers,1831-1997 (bulk 1907-1997).
Wormley, Edward J and Edward Crouse Papers, 1831-1997 (bulk 1907-1997)
Material relating to Edward Crouse's work at the University of Georgia is located at the Hargrett Rare and Manuscript Library, University of Georgia, Manuscript Collection #980.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Personal Records
  - Edward Crouse Personal Records
    - General biography, circa 1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Decease and estate, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Diaries and appointment books, 1960-1963, 1965, 1968, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 1-7)
    - Education
      - Grade school, 1915-1920 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Rochelle High School, 1922-1926 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - University of Wisconsin
        - Commencement, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
        - Coursework in English, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Coursework in history, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - Coursework in philosophy and logic, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - Drama and glee club, circa 1925-1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - Fraternity membership, circa 1925-1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Yale University, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Employment, 1929-1930, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Employment - University of Georgia, 1930-1946 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
    - Family Records
      - General, 1831-1896 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Annie Amelia Crouse decease and estate, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1896-1936 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Genealogy, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Genealogy - Daughters of the American Revolution material, 1900-1911 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Genealogy - Daughters of the American Revolution material, 1917-1947 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - William P. Landon writings, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Financial records, circa 1946-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Health and medical records, 1961-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Home and Property
      - Apartment at 10 Mitchell Place, New York, NY, 1968, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
      - Art and books, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Car accident, January 1968-April 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Car accident, October 1969-October 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Car accident, February 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Identifying documents, 1908-1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Identifying documents - passports, 1937-1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Legal records, 1933-1935 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Lists of lovers, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Military service, 1942-1946, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Military service - patches and medals, circa 1942-1946 (Box 27, Folder 3-6)
    - Military service - miscellaneous, circa 1942-1946 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Playbills from childhood theater productions ("The Colonial Theatre") 1922 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Sketches and designs, circa 1923-1939 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Sketches and designs - Weston, CT cottage, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Travel records, circa 1922-1937 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Writings, circa 1920 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Writings; "The Tiny Tribune," 1919-1922 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Writings - Tommy Hopkins Stories, circa 1921 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
    - Sheet music "Friendship" from DuBarry Was a Lady, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Joint Crouse/Wormley Personal Records
    - Education records - Rochelle High School yearbooks, 1922-1926 (Box 28, Folder 1-5)
    - Financial records, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Financial records - Swiss bank account, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Home and Property
      - Heritage Village condominiums, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Weston, CT Cottage
        - Furnishing and upkeep, 1957-1968, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 29-30)
        - Furnishing and upkeep, 1969-1975 (Box 13, Folder 25)
        - Kitchen remodeling, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - Landscaping, circa 1957-1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Legal and financial records, 1956-1969 (Box 13, Folder 26)
        - Security system, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 27)
        - Swimming pool, 1968-1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Travel Records
      - General, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - European tour, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 29-30)
      - Travel journal - Mexico trip, August 1953 (Box 27)
      - Travel scrapbooks - European tour, May-August 1971 (Box 26)
      - Travel scrapbook - European tour, February-March 1975 (Box 19)
      - West Indies trip, April 1950 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Edward J Wormley Personal Records
    - General biography, circa 1936-1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - General biography - Edward Wormley: The Other Face of Modernism, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Charitable giving, 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Commonplace book, circa 1922-1930 (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
    - Decease and estate, 1961-1989 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Diaries and appointment books, 1959-1990 (Box 27)
    - Diaries and appointment books, 1964-1968, 1972, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 10-18)
    - Education
      - Art Institute of Chicago
        - General, 1926-1927 (Box 13, Folder 32)
        - General, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 39)
        - Coursework, 1926-1927 (Box 13, Folder 33-34)
      - Rochelle High School, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Family Records
      - Certificate of Marriage of Edith and Myron J. Wormley, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Edith Wormley's correspondence, 1945-April 1948 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Edith Wormley's correspondence, May-June 1948 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - Edith Wormley's correspondence, July 1948-December 1949 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Edith Wormley's correspondence, 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Edith Wormley's correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Edith Wormley's decease and estate, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Edith Wormley miscellaneous, 1900, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Financial Records
      - Checkbooks, 1984-1988 (Box 25)
      - Heritage Village expense notebook, 1971-1975 (Box 24)
      - Taxes
        - Tax years 1935-1940, 1935-1941 (Box 13, Folder 35)
        - Tax year 1941, 1941-1946 (Box 13, Folder 36)
        - Tax year 1942, 1942-1944 (Box 13, Folder 37)
        - Tax year 1943, 1943-1946 (Box 13, Folder 38)
        - Tax year 1944, 1944-1947 (Box 13, Folder 39)
        - Tax year 1945, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 40)
        - Tax year 1946, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 41)
        - Tax year 1947, 1947-1952 (Box 13, Folder 42)
        - Tax year 1948, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 43)
        - Tax year 1949, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 44)
        - Tax year 1950, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 45)
        - Tax year 1951, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 46)
        - Tax year 1952, 1952-1955 (Box 13, Folder 47)
        - Tax year 1953, 1953-1959 (Box 13, Folder 48)
        - Tax year 1954, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 49)
        - Tax year 1955, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 50)
        - Tax year 1956, 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 51)
        - Tax year 1957, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 52)
        - Tax year 1958, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 53)
        - Tax year 1959, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 54)
        - Tax year 1961, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 55)
        - Correspondence with accountant, 1954-1959 (Box 13, Folder 56)
      - Tax and Expense Notebooks
        - 1979 (Box 19)
        - 1980 (Box 20)
        - 1982 (Box 21)
        - 1983 (Box 22)
        - 1985 (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Home and Property
      - Apartment at 450 E. 52nd St., New York, 1949-1964 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - Apartment inventory, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - Apartment plans and sketches, 1934-1938 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Art and books, circa 1967-1976 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - Stolen goods inventory, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970-1987 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Identifying documents, circa 1907-1987 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Insurance records, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Legal records - correspondence with Attorney (Barbara Zinsser), 1952-1986 (Box 13, Folder 57-61)
    - Magazine subscription list, 1945-1965 (Box 29, Folder 19-20)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Parties given, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Political contributions and correspondence, 1951-1991 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Travel records, 1951-1986 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Travel journal - trip to India, Japan, and South Korea, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 13, Folder 62-63)
    - Music by George Wood, circa 1960 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - News clippings, circa 1947-1970 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Obituary collection, circa 1927-1976 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Record album labelled "E. Wormley," undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Watercolors, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Wallet (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous personal records, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Correspondence between Crouse and Wormley
    - September-October 1925 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - November-December 1925 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - January-February 17, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - February 18-28, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - March 1-15, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - March 16-31, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - April 1926 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - May 1-18, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - May 19-31, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - June-August 1926 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - September-October 1926 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - November-December 1926 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - January 1927 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - February 1927 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - March 1927 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - April-May 1927 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - June-July 1927 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - August-October 1927 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - November-December 1927 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - January-May 1928 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - June-August 1928 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - September-December 1928 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1929 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - January-February 1930 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - March-July 1930 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - August-September 1930 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - October 1930 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - November-December 1930 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - January-April 1931 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - May-July 1931 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - August-December 1931 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - January-May 1932 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - July-September 1932 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - October-December 1932 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - January-April 1933 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - May-December 1933 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - January-May 1934 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - June-September 1934 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - October-December 1934 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - January 1935 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - February 1935 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - March 1935 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - April 1-10, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - April 11-30, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - May-June 1935 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - July-August 1935 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - September 1-24, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - September 25-30, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - October 1-15, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - October 16-31, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - November 1935 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - December 1935 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - January 1-10, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - January 11-20, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - January 21-26, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - January 27-31, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - February 1-15, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - February 15-29, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - March 1-20, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - March 21-31, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - April 1-10, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - April 11-30, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - May 1936 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - June 1936 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - August 1936 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - September 1936 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - October 1-20, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - October 21-31, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - November-December 1936 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - January 1-15, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - January 16-31, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - February 1-15, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - February 16-28, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - March 1937 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - April 1-15, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - April 16-30, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - May 1937 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - June 1-15, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - June 16-30, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - July-September 1937 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - October 1-19, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - October 20-31, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - November-December 1937 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - January 1-15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - January 16-31, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - February 1-15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - February 16-28, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - March 1-10, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - March 11-31, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - April 1938 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - May 1938 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - June 1-15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - June 16-30, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - July-September 1938 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - October 1-9, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - October 10-18, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - October 19-31, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - November 1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - December 1938 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - January 1-10, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - January 11-31, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - February 1-15, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - February 15-28, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - March 1-15, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - March 16-31, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - April 1-19, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - April 20-30, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - May 1939 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - June 1-15, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - June 16-30, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - July-August 1939 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - September 1939 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - October 1-9, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - October 10-31, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - November 1-13, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - November 14-31, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - December 1939 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - January 1-19, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - January 20-31, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - February 1-14, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - February 15-29, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - March 1940 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - April 1-19, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - April 20-30, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - May 1-10, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - May 11-21, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - June 1-14, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - June 15-30, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - July 1-19, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - July 20-31, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - August 1940 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - September 1-25, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - September 26-30, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - October 1-14, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - October 15-31, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - November 1940 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - December 1940 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - January 1-15, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - January 16-31, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - February 1941 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - March 1-20, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - March 21-31, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - April 1941 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - May 1941 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - June-September 1941 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - October 1941 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - November 1941 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - December 1941 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - January 1942 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - February 1942 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - March 1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - April 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - May 1942 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - June 1942 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - July 1942 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - September-November 1942 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - December 1942 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - January 1943 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - February 1943 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - March 1943 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - April 1943 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - May 1943 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - June 1-15, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - June 16-30, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - July 1943 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - August-October 1943 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - November 1943 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - December 1943 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - January-February 1944 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - March-May 1944 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - June-August 1944 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - September-December 1944 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - January 1945 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - February 1-19, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - February 20-28, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - March 1945 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - April 1945 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - May 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - June-July 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - August-September 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - March-April 1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - May 1946 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - June 1946 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - July-August 1946 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - September-October 1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - November 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - December 1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - January 1947 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - February 1947 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - January 1948 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 1949-1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Crouse addresses and address books, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Crouse Incoming Correspondence
    - Aronstam, H.J., 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Baker, Frederick C. ("Kitty"), circa 1939-1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Carithers, Eula, 1931-1932, 1957-1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Carithers, Eula, circa 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Christmas cards (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Clawson, Ruth and Hugh, circa 1923-1933 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Colby, Stuart and Mary, 1931-1944 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Crouse, Blanche, 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Crouse, Harvey S., 1924-1943 (Box 5, Folder 25-30)
    - Delle, John, 1934-1936 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Dillingham, Susan Grey, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Douglas, L.N., 1930-1936 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Eichelberger, Margaret Crouse and Robert, 1949-1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Gaguine, Frances Crouse, 1930-1931, 1936-1975 (Box 5, Folder 35-37)
    - Gaguine, Frances Crouse, 1932-1935 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Gallaway, John, 1934-1936 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Gerres, Charles, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Griswold, Margaret Crouse and Robert, 1930-1939 (Box 5, Folder 40-41)
    - Griswold, Susan Cass, circa 1960-1974 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Hall, William, circa 1942 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Hammack, William ("Bud"), 1935-1940 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Kempton, Grace and Willett Main, 1939-1954 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Kennedy, Jesse, circa 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Landon, William P. and Margaret, 1925-1934 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Lee, J.F., 1935 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Martin, Harold, 1931-1936 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Martin, Harold, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - McEwan, Margaret, 1936-1939 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - McEwan, Margaret, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - McKoin, Mary Nell ("Mak"), 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Myers, Sadie, July 1934-1939 (Box 5, Folder 52-54)
    - Nordhausen, George, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Owens, Hubert, 1932-1937 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Peck, Frederick G., 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Quinn, Paul, circa 1940-1943 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Reed, Grace Virginia, 1930-1934 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Salerno, Alfonso, 1931-1935 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Sohn, Louis, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Still, Bayrd, 1930-1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Talligant, Susan, 1936-1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Troutman, William, 1938-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Wallace, Dorothy ("Dort"), circa 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Wells, W.G. ("Horsie"), circa 1931-1934 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Wormley, Edith, 1931-1934 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Zasada, Marshall, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous chronological correspondence, 1918-1975, undated (Box 6, Folder 10-21)
    - Miscellaneous incoming correspondence, 1943-1945, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 70)
      from Parsons The New School for Design
  - Crouse Outgoing Correspondence
    - Landon, William P. and Margaret, circa 1924-1931 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous chronological correspondence, circa 1916-1945 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Joint addresses and Christmas card lists, 1965-1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Joint Incoming Correspondence
    - Bain, Gretchen K., 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Baker, Frederick C. ("Kitty"), circa 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Carney, Vincent, circa 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Delight, Mary, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - McEwan, Margaret, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Whitson, Maude, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Wood, George, circa 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous chronological correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 14, Folder 30-31)
  - Wormley address books, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Wormley Incoming Correspondence
    - Bain, Gretchen K. and William D., circa 1960-1982 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Baker, Frederick C., 1939-1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Beneduce, Antimo, 1942-1975 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Birthday cards, circa 1980-1990 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Bloum, Lotta, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Brandon, Hans and Kit, 1969-1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Braun, Edna W., 1974-1981 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Carney, Vincent and Mary, 1929-1980 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Christmas cards, 1959, 1968-1986, 1988-1989, 1991, 1994, undated (Box 6, Folder 41-54)
    - Edwards, Adra, and Dorothy Guerrette, circa 1960-1985 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Eichelberger, Margaret Crouse and Robert, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Fraser, Lou, circa 1970 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Gaguine, Frances Crouse, circa 1976-1988 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Glicksman, Joan, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Grisch, Roy C., 1948-1965 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Groves, Lowell, 1970-1982 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Gusten, Chaja and Theo, circa 1966-1974 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Holiday cards, circa 1976 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Keegan, Thomas and Ann, 1929-1980 (Box 6, Folder 64-65)
    - Jacobson, E., 1969-1980 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Laird, Anita and David, 1969-1979 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Laski, Viola, 1969-1979 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - McEwan, Margaret, circa 1972-1985 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Morgan, Randall, 1982-1987 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Rodgers, Grace and Martin, 1970-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Roudos, Justine, 1967-1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Seneker, Bea and Walter, 1961-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Shaeffer, Martha, circa 1960-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Sympathy for death of Edith Wormley, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 5-8)
    - Watterston, Kathleen and Henning, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Whitson, Maude, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Winders, Florence, 1961-1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Wood, George, circa 1972-1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Wormley, Cheryl and James, 1969-1978 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Wormley, Edith, circa 1930-1955 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Wormley, Myron and Frances, circa 1948-1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Yarling, Helen, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Chronological Correspondence
      - 1937-1949 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - 1950-1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - 1969 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - 1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - 1982-1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Wormley Outgoing Correspondence
    - Keegan, Thomas and Ann, 1950-1966 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Wormley, Edith, circa 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous chronological correspondence, 1931-1965 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Unidentified correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Series III. Edward J Wormley Professional Records
  - Subseries IIIA. Business Records
    - Dunbar Furniture Company